《越狱》  前情回顾
Previously on Prison Break.
从现在开始  我要求每个人
From now on, I'm asking
任何时候  都把卡放在
that everyone keep their card on them.
自己的身上
At all times.
格雷琴没拿到第六张卡
Gretchen didn't get us the sixth card.
那我们怎么办
So where does that leave us?
但格雷琴给了你一份资料
You know, Gretchen did pass on this one piece of information for you.
应该对你有帮助
It's gonna be helpful.
我接到一位老友的电话  听说"锡拉"有眉目
I got a call from an old friend, heard Scylla was
他想知道
in play and he wants to know
他能否弄到手  我找了个安全的地方
if he can get in on it. I've set up a safe house
在那可以跟他谈
where you can hear him out.
-你有笔吗  -等一下
Do you have a pen? Just a minute.
皮尔蒙特街1917号
1917 Piermt.
赛尔夫探员
Agent Self...
我们已恭候多时
we've been waiting.
斯科菲尔德和布伦斯从那扇门
When Scofield and Burrows walk
走出来  给他们一次
rough the door, give them
投降的机会
an opportunity to surrender.
他们不可能乖乖地束手就擒的
There's no way they're gonna hand it over without a fight.
如果他们动手  我们以牙还牙
If they take that position, we'll respond in kind.
我们走错一步
We make one wrong move,
监视器就会启动
the camera goes on,
克兰兹将军就会发现我们
And General  Krantz will know we're inside.
马上派一队人下去
I need a team downstairs now!
应该不会等很久
Shouldn't be long.
你确定我们不用下去等
You sure we shouldn't be waiting down there
迈克尔带着"锡拉"出来吗
for Michael to leave with Scylla.
如果你懂战术的话
If you knew anything about tactics,
这里就是所谓的制高点
you would know this is the high ground.
况且我们有消声器
Besides we have silencers.
"锡拉"不是一张卡
So, Scylla isn't one card.
而是六张
It's six.
确定他没带炸药后
Make sure he's not armed with explosives.
就杀了他
Then kill him.
把枪放下
Drop 'em.
不然  我就打爆他的头
Or I blow his head clean off.
你该把枪放下
You're gonna want to put that down.
你放不放
把枪放下
Lower your weapons.
快点  过去
Come on. Get over there.
快点  老头
Come on,old man.
由世上最聪明的人设计出的安全系统
The best minds in the world designed this security system,
你几乎把它打破了
and you almost beat it.
不用太伤心嘛
The frustration must be killing you.
你输定了
You blew it.
其实
Actually...
万事俱备  只欠东风
there's only one missing piece of the puzzle.
你正好把它带来了
And you just brought it to me.
我不知道你说的是什么
I'm not sure what you're talking about.
你的"锡拉"卡
Your Scylla card.
给我
Now.
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多字幕下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
字幕：YYeTs人人影视字幕组  后期：zwzy_1007(胖胖)
《越狱》第四季 第十二集
Prison.Break.S04E12
和你预想的不一样
Not what you expected?
我预想的是
What I expect
你占具这个系统的所有优势
of a man like you is a system where you've got all the advantage.
看起来  你缺几张卡
Looks like you're a few cards short.
想不到吧  将军
Suck it, General.
你是我见过的最差劲的拍档
You're the worst partner I've ever worked with.
-你说什么  -你让我
What? Leaving me
对付一个单手怪人
with the one-handed freak
和一个疯女人  你却和一群
and crazy bitch, while you hang out
-帅哥在一起  -闭嘴
with GQ... Be quiet.
-安静点  -别告诉我怎么做
Be quiet. Be quiet. Don't tell me what to do!
你是个懦夫
You're a coward!
听我说
Listen to me.
你以为格雷琴和巴格维尔会给你"锡拉"
You think Gretchen and Bagwell are gonna get you Scylla,
但他们的对手
but the people they're gonna steal it from
早有准备
have a plan
-闭嘴  -要骗他们
Shut up! to trick them...
-你闭嘴  -不要命令我
You shut up! Okay,be quiet.Don't tell me to shut up.
什么都不要告诉他
Don't tell him anything!
我想说什么就说什么
I can tell whatever I want!
-你给我安静  -别命令我
Be quiet! Don't tell me
让我闭嘴
to shut up!
别动
Don't!
我们需要他
We needed him.
他刚刚想杀你
He was going to kill you.
算了  去对付格雷琴和巴格维尔
All right, just go get Gretchen and Bagwell.
我来处理现场
m gonna take care of this.
科尔  你真该觉得脸红
Cole.you ought to be ashamed of youelf.
我不管你回家怎么做
I don't know how things worked back home,
但在这里  我们应该
but around here, we like to give
正式介绍一下我们的客人
our guest a proper introduction.
我叫格雷戈里·怀特  很高兴认识你
I'm Gregory White. Nice to meet you.
苏珊·安东尼
Susan Anthony.
这几天经常见你过来
I've seen you around the past couple of days.
你是我们的准客户吗
Are you a prospective client?
不是  我其实是科尔以前的同事
Actually, no, I am a former work colleague of Cole's.
她是个非常有说服力的销售员
She's a pretty convincing salesman herself.
真的
Really?
你们以前在哪合作过
Where did you work together?
佛罗里达
Florida.
Florida?
你以前不是在东北分区吗
Weren't you in the Northeast division?
以前是
I was.
但我在伽特的第一份工作
But my very first job with GATE was, uh,
是在克利尔沃特
in Clearwater.
看来你不喜欢久居一处  是吧
I guess you don't like to stay put much, do you?
天啊  我天生就是个好动之人
Lord, I was born a ramblin' man.
很高兴认识你
Well, it was, uh, wonderful to meet you. I, uh...
我得去开电话会议了
I have to go jump on a conference call.
他知道了
He knows.
不行  不行
No. No.
不行
No.
她有枪
She's got a gun!
把电话挂了
Hang it up.
快去那边  进怀特先生的办公室
Please, that way. Right in Mr. White's office.
所有人冷静
Everybody just stay calm.
-坐下  -进怀特先生的办公室
Sit!Mr. White's office!
仔细听着
Now listen very closely!
我们不想伤害任何人
No one's gonna get hurt.
现在怎样
Now what?
你到底
How...
怎么得到五张卡的
did you get all five cards?
不用太伤心嘛
The frustration must be killing you.
是它吗
Is that...?
那是什么
What is that?
那些卡都是钥匙
The cards were keys...
这个
...and this...
这个才是锡拉
this is Scylla.
你现在应该
Guess right now you wish
后悔陷害我们了吧  将军
you'd framed somebody else, huh, General?
你们是出不去的
You're not even close to getting out of here.
我们走
Let's go.
哥们  你确定吗
You sure, Papi?
我们不知道原路返回会怎样
We have no idea what's waiting for us back there.
对  但我们也不知道往上走会怎样
Yeah, but we don't know what's be up there
相信我
either. Trust me.
将军  我们需要你
General, we're gonna need you
来启动电梯
to activate this elevator.
祝你们好运
Best of luck.
你得跟我们一起走
You're coming with us.
没事的  德曼尼  放下枪
It's all right, Damani. Put away the gun.
一切尽在掌控之中
Everything's under control.
红色警报
We have a major situation.
迈克尔  谢天谢地
Michael, thank God.
我们搞定了
We got it.
你那边怎么样
How's it going on your end?
非常好
Pretty damn good.
再给我五分钟
But give me five more minutes.
你告诉怀特杀我儿子时
Is that the desk
就坐在这里吗
you sat at when you told Wyatt to kill my son?
放心吧  阿历克斯
Don't worry, Alex.
过了今天  他就不会再发号施令了
He won't be giving any more orders after today.
我很好奇
I'm curious.
你们认为你们能出去吗
How do you think you're getting out of here?
我们
The second
走出电梯时
we stepped off the elevator,
我的警卫就下令封锁了整幢大楼
my guard made a call to put the entire building under lockdown.
禁止一切出入
Nothing gets in or out.
不管你们在等什么
So whatever you're waiting for
都不会来了
it isn't coming.
你在看什么
What are you looking at, huh?
没有  什么都没有
Nothing. Nothing.
你在看什么
Huh? What are you looking at?!
什么都没有
Nothing.
别老瞪着我  回去
Don't you be eyeballing me, soldier.Back to work.
我们不可能搞定了
There's no way this is gonna end well.
我们应该离开这里
We should get out of here.
等20分钟赚1.25亿美金不值吗
Don't you think it's worth 20 minutes for $125 million?
闭嘴吧
Suck it up!
派一队人守在在将军办公室外
I want a team outside of the General's office.
我们必须解决这事
We need to get a handle on this.
检查电梯
Check the elevator.
把守楼梯
Cover the stairwell.
设计这么多就为了保密一些姓名和报告吗
All that design just to hold some names and reports.
姓名和报告
Names and reports?
这是政府还是你父亲告诉你们的
Is that informatn from the government,or your father?
小心点
Careful.
右边最上层抽屉
Top right-hand drawer.
有你感兴趣的东西
It's something that should be of interest to you.
出现你们的名字时  我调出来的
I pulled it when your names came up.
你为什么离开
Why did you leave?
我在一个跨国集团
I took a position
找了一份工作
with a group of multinationals we call
我们称之为"公司"
the Company.
他们决定这个国家的一切
They call every shot this country takes.
你们出生前  我就认识你们父亲
I knew your father since before you were born
你们知道他曾为"公司"卖命
You do know he worked for the Company?
对  他是个数据分析家
Yeah. He was data analyst.
他是这样跟你说的吗
Is that what he told you?
也有道理
Well, it makes sense.
他想保护你们  远离真相
He wanteto protect you from the truth.
我警告你
I'm warning you.
你父亲是个聪明人
Your father was a brilliant man,
但他绝不可能击垮"公司"
but he could never have defeated the Company.
你们没必要像他一样
You don't have to make the same
犯愚蠢的致命错误
misguided, fatal mistake that he did.
你们对"公司"知之甚少
There's so much you don't know about the Company...
还有锡拉
about Scylla...
你父亲
about your dad...
还有你母亲
about your mother.
我发誓  我会杀了你
I swear to God, I'll kill you.
放松点
Let's get through this.
计划是什么
What's the plan?
赛尔夫探员
Agent Self?
进行如何
Where are we?
他们进去大约2个小时了
The men went in about two hours ago.
还不确定他们是否得到锡拉了吗
No confirmation on whether they've gotten Scylla?
还没有  不过我保证  贺勃
Not yet, but I promise you, Herb,
我第一个告诉你  好吧
you'll be the first to know, okay?
一旦得到消息  我会开一辆无牌车
And as soon as I get word, I'm taking an unmarked car
去接头点  然后我再回来
to the pickup location, and then I'm gonna head back over...
不  你直接去达洛斯议员办公室
No. You go directlyto Senator Dallow's office
我会让检察长在那等着
I'll have the attorney general standing by.
我们不能临时改变计划
We can't veer from the plan here.
太危险了
It's too dangerous.
明白
Yes, sir.
就快结束了
We're almost at the finish line.
我知道
I know.
我没想到你能查到这么深
I never thought you'd make it this far.
我错了
I was wrong.
我们要做好准备
We need to be prepared to go in
随时待命
as soon as the General gives the order.
你们想要什么
What is it you all want?
费尔南多
Fernando.
只要开口
Just say the word,
你女儿的
and your little girl's
学费就能解决
college education is paid for.
我们会给她买幢房子  好好生活
We'll buy her a house to grow up in.
你以为只要
You think you can just
向我们撒点钱
throw some cash at us, huh?
我们就会忘掉一切吗
We'll forget everything, call it a day?
潘姆需要你  阿历克斯
Pam needs you, Alex.
此刻更是如此
Now more than ever.
你们都很伤心
You're both still hurting,
但时间是良药
but given time, it'll pass.
也许过段日子你们又可以
And maybe some day you'll be ready
为人父母  钱不在话下
to be parents again, and if money is no object.
你应该听听自己
You should hear yourself right now.
现在声音多绝望
The desperation in your voice.
你听到了吗
You hear it?
好好考虑我说的话
But listen to what it is I'm saying.
离我远点
Get away from me.
你想要的一切
Whatever you want...
离我远点
Get away from me.
你们想要的一切
Whatever you want,
我都可以提供
I can provide.
你和莎拉
Airline tickets
可以乘飞机票去任何地方
for u and Sara anywhere in the world.
我想要的是
What I want
目睹公司化为灰烬
is to see The Company burn to the ground,
而你  锒铛入狱
and you in prison.
这就是我们想要的
It's what we all want.
这是不可能的
That'll never happen.
-你最近怎么样  -很好
-Hi. How have you been?  -Good.
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
一边去
Please back off.
让我来帮你
Excuse me. Let me help you
擦掉那些东西
get some of that off.
住手  只要
You know what? Stop. Just...
不要担心
Don't worry about it.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
失陪  先生们
Excuse me, gentlemen.
谢谢
Thank you.
该死
Damn it.
所有人就位
Everybody get into position.
很快一切都会结束
This is going to end
结局不会乐观
very soon, and it's not going to be pretty.
最后一次机会
One last chance.
把"锡拉"留下
Leave Scylla, and you can all
你们都自由了
go free.
只管从这扇门出去
Just walk out the door.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
你杀了我  然后呢
You shoot me, and then what?
从19层高的办公室窗户跳下去吗
You jump out the window of my 19th floor office?
迈克尔  你杀了我就没了筹码
Michael, you kill me, you lose your levera.
喂
Hello?
为你准备的
It's for you.
这又是什么
Oh, what is this?
筹码
Leverage.
是我
It's me.
丽莎
Lisa?
我在枪口上
I'm at gunpoint.
怎么回事
What's going on?
是唐克雷蒂
It's Tancredi.
她说  你要是不让迈克尔
She says if you don't
和其他人带着"锡拉"离开  她就杀了我
let Michael and the others leave with Scylla, she'll kill me.
爸爸
Dad?
求你
Please.
按他们说的做
Do what they want.
将军  我建议你采纳你女儿的建议
I suggest you take your daughter's advice, General.
你个混蛋
You son of a bitch.
丽莎  你在哪
Lisa, where you are?
让她听电话
Get her back on the phone!
我们离开后你可以跟你女儿通话
You can talk to your daughter after we've left
当然  是带着"锡拉"一起离开
with Scylla, of course.
据说你女朋友
Look, I read enough intel on your girlfriend
连只苍蝇也不会杀
to know that she wouldn't hurt a fly.
3个月前还有可能
Maybe three months ago.
但现在她变了
but she's changed.
我们都变了
We've all changed.
这是你杀的所有人的名单
This is a list of everyone you've killed.
父辈  子女  朋友
Fathers, sons, friends.
你真的认为
Do you really think
你女儿的性命比他们的值钱吗
your daughter's life is worth any more than theirs?
现在只有两个选择
One of two things is going to happen now.
放我们走  或者牺牲丽莎
You're going to let us go, or Lisa will die.
任选其一
Either one is fine with me.
不要伤害她
Just don't hurt her.
只要你信守诺言  我们就不伤人
As long as you hold up your end of the deal, we won't.
你下过令要转移"锡拉"
You ordered Scylla to be moved.
让我们体验一下吧
Show us how.
我跟他们出去
I'm walking them out!
退后
Stand down.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
他们肯定找到另外的出路
They must have found another way out.
不可能  那他们就被抓住或者死了
That's impossible. Well, then, they're caught or dead.
我们还要等多久
How much longer are we gonna wait?
是你说斯科菲尔德已经计划好了
You were the one who said Scofield had a plan.
是你用枪指着怀特先生
And you put a gun in Mr. White's face!
他会报警的
He was going to call the police.
别出声  没事的  我是联邦探员
Shh, shh. It's okay. It's okay. Federal agent.
什么
What?
快点  我会救你们的
Quick. I'll help you.
快点  给他们解开
Quick. Help me untie the others.
我盯着科尔和那个女人
Okay, I'll keep an eye on Cole and the woman.
你们一次两个人溜出去
I want you to slip out two at a time.
你们两个先走
Okay, you two first.
为什么不能一起走
Why can't we all go together?
你在这儿  去抓他们
You're here. Go arrest them.
我想在他们发现之前
I want to get out as many of you as possible
尽可能多的救你们出去
before they realize what's happening.
帝博格·巴格维尔因谋杀被通辑
Theodore Bagwell's wanted for murder.
现在科尔·普发又成了绑架犯
Now Cole Pfeiffer's a hostage-taker.
我该怎么办
What am I gonna do?
你得一辈子逃命
You're gonna run for your life,
你个白痴
you idiot.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
不  怀特先生
No, Mr. White.
不  怀特先生  等等
No, Mr. White. Wait!
不  等一下
No! Wait!
所有人趴下  放下武器
Everybody stay down! Drop your weapon!
打911
Call 911!
感觉如何
How does it feel, huh?
被迫做不想做的事
Being forced to do something you don't want to do?
但如果你不照做
But knowing that if you don't go through with it,
你关心的人就会遭殃
someone you care about is gonna suffer;
他们会付出代价
they're gonna pay?
种什么因  得什么果  将军
What goes around, comes around, huh, General?
我
I...
我无法想象你经历的事
I can't imagine what you've been through.
我无法想象你想做的事
I can't imagine that you'd want to.
不论他们对你做了什么
Whatever they've done to you...
你就是他们  我的朋友
"They" are you, my friend.
不论他们跟你说了什么
Whatever they've told you,
你必须明白
you need to realize that...
斯科菲尔德和布伦斯是坏人
Scofield and Burws are bad men.
你以前是个医生
You used to be a doctor.
你一生都在帮助别人
You devoted your whole life help other people.
现在看看你
Now look at you.
他们让你用枪指着一个无辜的女人
They have you holding a gun on an innocent woman.
你是无辜的
So you're innocent?
你只是
You're jus..
处理数据
crunching numbers and running data
让世界变得更美好
to make the world a better place?
德巴克夫人
Mrs. Tabak?
你很好
You're fine.
你还需要几分钟
You need a couple of minutes.
德巴克夫人  你在吗
Hello, Mrs. Tabak?!
你还好吗
You okay?
说
Say it.
我在洗我的裙子
I'm soaking my skirt.
我要是给洗衣店前不把油弄出来
If I d't get the grease out before it gets to the cleaners,
衣服就毁了
it'll be ruined.
好的  夫人
Okay, ma'am.
我不知道在你的象牙塔里是什么情景
I don't know what it looks like up there in your ivory tower.
而底下的人都要死了
Down on the ground, men and women are dying
生活被毁掉
and lives are being ruined.
所以  我会做任何事情
So, I'm prepared to do absolutely anything
来阻止你
in order to stop you.
转过去
Turn around.
转过去  丽莎
Turn... around, Lisa.
你该让我去说服怀特先生
You should've let me try to convince Mr. White
就不会发生这一切
that everything was gonna be okay.
那样的话  我就能
That way, I could've...
能怎样  每天穿着西装
What?! Put on a monkey suit every day
坐在办公桌后吗
and sit behind a desk.
你以为你还能坚持多久
How long you think that's gonna last?
你想拿着MP-5上大街上吗
You gonna walk down the street with an MP-5?
你不是认真的吧
You can't be serious.
他们能认出你  科尔
They can identify you, Cole.
你是唯一把我跟绑架联系起来的人
You're the only one linking me to that crime scene.
但是  跟你合作很愉快
But, hey, it was nice working with you.
不许动
Don't move!
转过去
Turn around.
Turn around!
温柔点  甜心
Gently now, sugar.
我是米里亚姆·贺尔兹探员  甜心
That's Special Agent Miriam Holtz to you, sugar.
走吧
Let's go.
我要跟我女儿通话
I want to speak with my daughter
确认她已经被释放
get confirmation that she's being released.
莎拉会一直监禁你女儿
Sara will be keeping your daughter in custody
直到她确定我们已安全离开
until she knows we're safely away from this place
也没人跟踪
with nobody trailing us.
公司的探员不只深入到联调局
Company agents aren't just embedded in the FBI
和情报机构
and the Secret Service.
他们深入执法机关  医院  车管所
They're in local law enforcement, hospitals, DMV.
你永远看不到我们在哪
You'll never see us coming.
实际上  一旦我们把"锡拉"交给正确的人
Actually, once we get Scylla into the right hands,
你所有的探员和行动
alyour agents, all your operations--
都会公之于众
it'll all be out in the open,
那时  人人都能看到你们
and then everyone... will see you coming.
这是我们干的
We did this to you.
我们干的
别忘了  老头
Don't you forget that, old man.
想知道你父亲替公司干过什么吗
Want to know what your father really did for the Company?
他是个刽子手
He was an executioner.
他杀掉所有背叛公司的人
He killed people who defected from the company.
而他训练的人会追杀你们
now the men he trained will be coming after you.
跟我来  有点不对劲
Come on. Something's not right.
德巴克女士
Mrs. Tabak?
Mrs. Tabak?!
她刚走
She just left.
唐克雷蒂  她肯定没走远
Tancredi.she has to be right outside.
你还好吗
Are you all right?
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
我现在赶回来
I'm heading back now.
不  我要你待在安全的地方
No. I want you in a secure location,
有人监护你
under supervision.
你先回家
You go home.
但我必须过去
But I really need to be there.
我们一拿回"锡拉"  就给你打电话
I'll call you once we get Scylla back
我们把那辆卡车的牌照和识别码
We've given the truck's license plate and VIN number
报给当地警局了
to the local police...
一旦斯科菲尔德破解出标准操作程序
We lost our tactical initiative the minute
我们就失去了战术主动权
that Scoeld figured out our SOPs.
我们要打败他
If we want to defeat him,
就必须打破陈规  出其不意
we've got to alter our way operating become unpredictable.
是他们  迈克尔  你们在哪
It's them.Michael,where are you?
在公司的装甲车上
The Company's armored truck.
我们拿到了
We have it.
他们拿到了
They got it.
听着  迈克尔  保持警惕  好吧
Okay, listen. Michael, stay on alert, okay?
我会的
I will.
我们在约定地点见
See you at the rendezvous.
你们去安全的地方
You guys get someplace safe.
等我们的消息
Wait till you hear from us.
-明白  -祝好运  伙计
You got it. Good luck, Bobby.
他们在哪
Where are they?
机场  我们看到他们了
The airport. We have visual confirmation.
抓到他们之前
Make sure not a single plane leaves the ground
别让任何一架飞机离开机场
before we've got them.
明白  长官
Understood, sir.
看紧斯科菲尔德和布伦斯
Stay with Scofield and Burrows.
"锡拉"最重要
Scylla's the priority.
女士们先生们  请注意
Attention, ladies and gentlemen,
由于技术故障  所有航班
due to technical issues, all flights have been
暂时无法起飞
temporarily grounded.
看
Check it out.
他们就在后面
They're right behind us.
我们上
Let's go.
现在
Now.
我叫约翰·伯顿
Hey, my name's John Burton.
我是非当班的芝加哥警察
I'm an off-duty cop from Chicago.
听着  我正经过安大略机场
Listen, I'm walking through Ontario Airport,
2号集散站  就在票务柜台旁
Terminal 2, right by the ticket counters
我发现有情况
and I just saw something
你们一定要查一下
that you guys definitely want  check out.
有人过来了
We got company.
迈克尔·斯科菲尔德和林肯·布伦斯
Michael Scofield and Lincoln Burrows.
我们走
Let's get out of here.
慢着
No, no, no...
你不会想要跑的
The last thing you want to do right now is run
怎么  你会开枪吗
Why is that? You gonna shoot us?
没错
Yeah.
一声令下  我的人就会把你们带走
I say the word and my men will take you both out.
在这么多人面前吗
In front of all these people?
你们不敢这么张扬的
You'd never risk that kind of exposure.
我觉得现在已经很明朗了
I think it's clear by now
你错误估计我们的限度了
that you've miscalculated how far we're willing to go.
把包给我
Give me the bag.
马上就把包给我
Give me the bag. Now.
告诉克兰兹事情还没完
Tell Krantz this isn't finished.
你可以亲自告诉他
Oh, you can tell him in person.
先生  请跟我们来
Sir? Please come with us.
怎么了
Excuse me?
安全检查而已
Just a security precaution.
好吧  没问题
Yeah, sure.
真的有必要吗
Is this really necessary?
请把包里的东西都拿出来
Please empty the contents of your bag.
我包里就一台电脑
Look, all I've got in there is a laptop
和一个外接硬盘而已
and an external hard drive.
告诉你  你们抓错人了
I'm telling you, you've got the wrong guy.
先生  放开包
Let go of the bag, sir.
[善终为善]
All's well that ends well.
如何
Well?
我们拿着呢
Yeah, we got it.
这么说你一开始就知道我是谁
So you knew who I was from the start, huh?
我的真实姓名  我的记录
My real name, my record...
我看过你的档案  没错
I read your file, yeah.
如果你没看过呢
What if you hadn't?
你想说什么
What's your point?
如果你不知道
What if you never knew
我是杀人犯帝博格·巴格维尔呢
I was Theodore Bagwell, the convict?
你会不会相信我是科尔·普发
Would you have believed I was Cole Pfeiffer?
顶级销售员
Stellar salesman...
天才演说家
talented speaker?
不知道
I don't know.
但你确实骗了不少人
You certainly had a lot of other people fooled, though.
在你拿枪指着他们之前
Till you pled a machine gun on them.
我想这就像是他们在伽特所说的
I guess it's like they said over at GATE:
我们都是自我的俘虏
"We are captives of our own identities,
禁锢在自己创造的监狱里
living in prisons of our own creation."
谁会想到此话
Who would've thought they'd actually
一语中的
be right about something?
你要是把它弄丢了
So if you drop this,
我们是不是都得回监狱
does that mean we all go back to prison?
别担心
Don't worry.
要是让它落入坏人手中
If this doesn't get in the right hands in one piece,
我的处境也会跟你们一样
I'm going to be in as bad a spot as you are.
恭喜你们
Congratulations.
怎样
What now?
我要遵守我之前的承诺
Now, I live up to my end of the deal.
半小时后  有辆车会来接你们
The vans are going to be here in a half an hour.
去驻外办事处
They're going to be sent to a field office
按程序搞掂一切
where you can go through processing.
这是你们的迁移文件
Th is all your transfer papework.
拿这个去找施密特探员
Get this to an Agent Schmidt.
他会护送你们安全离开
He's going to be heading up the convoy.
我很想亲自送你们
I wish I could drive you myself,
但我得尽快赶到达洛斯那边去
but I need to get to Dallow ASAP.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
还好
Yeah, I'm okay.
不  他不好
No, he's not.
他需要去医院
He needs to go to a hospital.
我再安排一辆救护车过来
All right, I'm going to send an ambulance with the vans.
给你安排最好的医疗救治
You're going to get the best medical care available.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不  应该感谢你们才对
No, I should be thanking you.
由于你们的功劳
Okay, because of what you've done,
生活将从此改变
lives are going to be changed forever.
再安排一辆救护车一起过来
Listen, I need a, uh, ambulance to come with the convoy.
长官  下一步怎么办
Sir, what are your orders?
长官
Sir?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们再也没有后顾之忧了
None of us will ever have to look over our shoulders again.
这是最重要的
That's the most important thing.
不管将来如何
No matter what comes next.
迈克尔  你不会有事的
You're gonna make it, Michael.
你做完手术
You'll have the operation and,
就会好起来的
and you'll get through this.
就像我们这一路走来一样
Just like we've gotten through everything else.
她很担心你
She's worried about you.
我很开心下一次想喝酒的时候
It's nice to know that the next time I want to drink one of these,
不用在这破仓库里喝
I won't have to drink it in this crappy warehouse.
没错
Yeah.
我都不记得上次坐在餐厅或去打球
I can't even remember being able to sit down at a restaurant
是什么感觉了
or go to a ball game.
天啊  就像这辈子都在逃亡
God... it seems like I've been running forever.
现在该停下来
But time to stand still.
好好享受了
Take in the sun.
干杯
Salud.
我知道现在应该开心才对
I know I'm supposed to be happy right now.
但我还是很害怕
I'm still scared.
我害怕经历过这么多
I'm scared we're going to have come all this way
我还会失去你
and I'm going to lose you anyway.
过来
Come here.
Come on.
莎拉
Sara...
别跟我说
Just don't tell me
一切都会好起来
that everything's going to be okay, please.
好的
Okay.
我不会说的
I won't.
你把你的"朋友"带来了
I see you brought your friend along.
格雷琴呢
What happened to Gretchen?
她跑了
Uh, she got away.
就是这个
So here it is.
什么
Wha...?
天啊
Oh, my God.
简直不敢相信
Wow. I can't believe it
接下来呢
So what's next?
找达洛斯议员
Senator Dallow?
不  我还需要处理一些琐事
No, I need to tie up some loose ends.
格雷琴和巴格维尔提过"锡拉"的其他事吗
Did Gretchen and Bagwell say anything else about Scylla
-例如其他买主  -冯
in terms of other buyers? Feng.
他已经死了
He's dead.
他们没和其他人说过吗
They didn't talk to anyone else?
我们要尽量搜集证据
We need to get as many indictments
指控他们
on this thing as possible.
巴格维尔可能知道
Well, Bagwell might know.
只要在审问时给他点甜头
Once we get him in an interview room and offer him a deal,
他就会说的
his mouth will start moving.
还记得我们来的第一天我说的话吗
Remember what I said to you the first day we got here?
记得  你说等这一切结束了
Yeah, you said that when this was over,
我们再做个了断
we were gonna settle up.
我们已经两清了
We're settled.
迈克尔
Michael.
都一个小时了
It's been an hour.
你能给赛尔夫打电话看救护车什么时候来吗
Would you call Self and check on that ambulance?
他不接电话吗
Is he not picking up?
可能是信号不好
Maybe something's wrong with the signal.
你所拨打的电话不在服务区
The number you have reached is not in service at this time
此号码为空号
and there is no new number.
怎么了
What is it?
你做的很好  米里亚姆
You did really good on this one, Miriam.
你很坚强
You really held your own.
谢谢夸奖
Thank you.
我能仔细看看那东西吗
Can I take a closer look at that?
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
赛尔夫
Self.